

CONTACT

WEBSITE: www.archiesanders.nl

EMAIL ADDRESS: 406738@vistacollege.nl

ARCHIE SANDERS

Software Developer

EDUCATION

Vista College Software Developer MBO4

September 2020 - present

I'm a year 2 Software development student at Vista College in Heerlen. The study takes 4 years to complete. We've worked on web-based applications, website's and made basic applications.

Trevianum Havo 4

September 2019 – June 2020

I went to this school for 1 year, but once covid started I couldn't finish my year, so I had to go to MBO.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Media INN Software Developer Internship January 2021 – July 2021

This was an internship for school where we got tasked to make an augmented reality application that could be utilized in the education system and would be used as a learning tool.

Bouwmaat auxiliary force

February 2022 - present

My job is to coordinate my colleagues, so they know what to do and make sure everyone is busy with their work. I also work at the service desk to help customers out with any of their need that is in reach of our ability.

SKILLS

HTML, CSS, PHP & JS: Making responsive webpages.

Python, C#: Making of basic applications.

SQL: Making of databases and executing queries.

ABOUT ME

I'm 19 years old, from Born, Limburg, the Netherlands. I currently study software development. My hobbies are playing games, going out friends and just socialize a lot. I live at home with my parents and younger sister, and we have 2 dogs. I really like to be motivated and active with what I'm doing and whenever I'm busy with something I try my best to finish it in having the best result in the end-product. I'm open to new ideas and always try my best to make a compromise if needed. I see myself more as a team player meaning that I always strive to keep the best possible communication and integration of my colleagues making sure that everyone is involved and busy with their task. I see teamwork as something that can inspire new ideas and opportunities for the whole team.